homeclick.com 2007-11-22

# Homeclick Security Policies

|  |  |  | 

[Customer Service](http://www.homeclick.com/web/customerservice/default.aspx) > Legal Policies

|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
| Welcome to HomeClick.com. HomeClick.com and its affiliates provide their services to you subject to the following conditions. **If you visit or shop at HomeClick.com, you accept these conditions**  
|   
Pricing Policy  
Privacy Policy  
Security Policy  
Safe Shopping Guarantee |  |  |   
|   
**Pricing Policy**

Despite our best efforts, a small number of the items in our catalog may be mispriced. If we discover a mispricing, we will do one of the following: 

  1. If an item's correct price is lower than our stated price, we will charge the lower amount and ship you the item. 
  2. If an item's correct price is higher than our stated price, we will, at our discretion, either contact you for instructions before shipping or cancel your order and notify you of such cancellation. 

back to top |   
|   
**Privacy Policy**

**Use Of Information**   
Currently HomeClick.com gathers customer information to improve the content on our website, to enhance your online shopping experience, and for marketing and promotional purposes. At the present time, this includes customer information specifically and knowingly provided by customers in the course of sales transactions on our site and provided by customers in response to surveys or other requests for information. Examples of such information are: name, postal address, email address, phone number and product commentary. 

When you make a purchase from HomeClick.com, we will ask for information such as name, address and credit card information. This information is stored in a secured database, only accessible to employees with access rights to this information. User's credit information is transferred over a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) line. This ensures your information is encrypted and cannot be read by any other Internet users. The secure mode begins upon ordering. To check to make sure that information is encrypted, a tiny padlock icon will appear at the bottom of your browser, letting you know information is being sent over a secured connection.

At times we may partner with outside vendors to provide additional services or products outside those offered by HomeClick.com. Should you choose to accept or subscribe to offers from third parties, we may pass your relevant personal information, including name and credit card number, to the third party whose offer you have accepted. Your information will be transferred securely, and as a convenience, you will not need to re-enter your personal information. Your acceptance of a third party offer gives HomeClick.com implied permission to share your personal information. Your personal information will not be released without your permission, as evidenced by your acceptance or subscription to an outside third party offer.

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in with a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users in order to enhance their experience on our site. 

**Log Files**   
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements on the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing**   
HomeClick will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. You may request not to receive any marketing material by sending an email to [webmaster@HomeClick.com](mailto:webmaster@HomeClick.com).

**Links**   
This website contains links to other sites. Please note that HomeClick.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites. 

back to top

|   
|   
**Security Policy**

HomeClick.com takes precautions to protect information about our users. When a customer places an order via our website, the information is encrypted and is protected using SSL (Secure Socket Layer).

When you are on a secure web page, the lock icon at the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked when you are just 'surfing' in an unsecured mode. 

back to top

|   
|   
**Safe Shopping Guarantee**

We guarantee that every online transaction you make will be 100% safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your credit card as a result of shopping at our online store. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, we will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made while using our secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. 

back to top

|
